inventa.com 2011-06-17

# Privacy Policy

This statement applies to information we collect from www.inventa.com and any other sites on the World Wide Web owned and/or operated by Inventa Technologies, inc. This statement is part of our terms and conditions and is subject to all of its provisions. 

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact: 

**Inventa Technologies, inc.**  
2040 Briggs Road, Suite B4  
Mount Laurel,  New Jersey 08054  
Attn: Legal Department 

Phone: 856-914-5200

Email: [privacy@inventa.com](mailto:privacy@inventa.com)

**Collection of Information**   
We collect non-personally identifiable information about you in a number of ways, including tracking your activities through your IP address or most-recently-visited URL. However, we do not collect any personally identifiable information about you unless you voluntarily submit contact information to us, such as by filling out a form or survey, registering your email address with us or emailing us. We may also collect personal information from you at other points on our site that state that personal information is being collected. We do not wish to obtain personally identifiable information from children who are using our site unsupervised. Thus, we ask children to obtain the consent of their parent or guardian before providing us with any personally identifiable information. 

**Disclosure of Information**  
Unless we tell you otherwise, we do not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to any third parties. 

**Use of Information**  
We use personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information for internal marketing purposes, for trend analysis, for pattern detection, and for site administration. However, unless we tell you otherwise, we do not use personally identifiable information collected from the website to send unsolicited mailings to you. Of course, if applicable, we do use personally identifiable information to perform the services for which such data was collected (i.e., if you sign up for an email newsletter, we will send the email newsletter to the address you provide us). 

**Third Party Sites**  
This policy only addresses our activities from our servers. Other sites (including those that we link to within an advertisement, article or otherwise, and third party sites or services with which we co-brand) may have their own policies, which we do not control, and thus are not addressed by this policy. 

**Review and Removal of Your Personally Identifiable Data**  
If you provide us with personally identifiable information to have us perform ongoing services to you, usually we will provide you with a way to review the information we have on file and either change or remove such data. To do so, please notify us via post or email at the address above and we will provide you with your contact information for review. To make changes, send us the changes. Unfortunately, to the extent that such information is also stored in other databases, we cannot always ensure that such corrections or deletions will reach the other databases. If you wish to have information you provided to us online removed from our records, please provide us with the information as you submitted it to us at the address above. We will use all reasonable efforts to ensure that your information is removed from our records. 

**Cookies and Other Tracking Methods**   
When you view our website, we might store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a “cookie” or similar file. Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive, not on our site. Cookies do not spy on you or otherwise invade your privacy, and they cannot invade your hard drive and steal information. Rather, they help you navigate a website as easily as possible. Cookies can help us provide information that is targeted to your interests and they allow us to better understand how users use our site, which in turn helps us focus our resources on features that are most popular with our users. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but some parts of our site, including our registered customer account web sites may not work properly in that case. 

**Security**   
We use industry-standard methods to protect your personally identifiable information from unauthorized access. Among other techniques, we usually store such information on a computer behind our “firewall” in a secure location, and we often restrict the number of employees internally who can access such data. Of course, there is no such thing as “perfect security” on the Internet. 

**Amendments**   
Amendments to this policy will be posted at this URL and will be effective when posted.
